<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Posts on A. Brown Blogdown</title>
		<link>/posts/</link>
		<description>Recent content in Posts on A. Brown Blogdown</description>
		<generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>&amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
		<item>
			<title>About Me and The Blog</title>
			<link>/posts/about-me-and-the-blog/</link>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
			
			<guid>/posts/about-me-and-the-blog/</guid>
			<description>Hi ThereThis is my initial post! I am grateful to have a space to share my thoughts and data explorations.
In This BlogI’d like to talk about data and analytic and the occasional random rant about things. I will try to express data and my thoughts eleantly (but no promises).
ProfessionallyI conisder myself an Experiened Data Professional. I’ve been drawn to data since I started my professional-working career in 2013.</description>
			<content type="html"><![CDATA[
<link href="/rmarkdown-libs/anchor-sections/anchor-sections.css" rel="stylesheet" />
<script src="/rmarkdown-libs/anchor-sections/anchor-sections.js"></script>


<div id="hi-there" class="section level1">
<h1>Hi There</h1>
<p>This is my initial post! I am grateful to have a space to share my thoughts and data explorations.</p>
</div>
<div id="in-this-blog" class="section level1">
<h1>In This Blog</h1>
<p>I’d like to talk about data and analytic and the occasional random rant about things. I will try to express data and my thoughts eleantly (but no promises).</p>
</div>
<div id="professionally" class="section level1">
<h1>Professionally</h1>
<p>I conisder myself an Experiened Data Professional. I’ve been drawn to data since I started my professional-working career in 2013. I became embarrising good at Excel, started creating complex queries, then developing repoducible code to automate data processing and reporting tasks in open source lanages like <code>Python</code> and <code>R</code>, as well as, cloud techonlogies like AWS.</p>
<p>I double majored in Supply Chain Management and Economics from the University of Northern Iowa and the got my Masters of Science from the University of Iowa.</p>
<p>I have interest in automation and machine learning, as well as, data strategy development and implementation.</p>
<p>I’ve worked in an elcectic of domains including distribution, k-12 standarized testing, and finance.</p>
</div>
<div id="personally" class="section level1">
<h1>Personally</h1>
<p>While I truely enjoy working with data, and it tends to seep into all aspects of my life, I also deeply enjoy spending time with my wife and dog.</p>
<p>(insert picture of wife and dog)</p>
<p>We like to get outdoors for hiking, camping, biking, kayaking, and running. I also like cooking and guitar.</p>
<p>Cheers, A. Brown</p>
</div>
]]></content>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
